faith.co.uk 2010-05-16

# Privacy Policy

At Faith we have adopted the following privacy policy as part of our commitment to protect any Personal Information which you may provide to us through this website or by other means. Please note that this privacy policy does not apply to other websites which may be linked through this website. Personal Information which you choose to provide to other websites will be subject to the privacy policies of those websites.

We will respect your personal data and will not share the information you give us with any third parties without your prior consent. We will only use the information you provide to monitor and improve our service to you and for marketing and promotional purposes.

  * Faith will not use or disclose your Personal Information unless you have given your permission, except for the following purposes: 
    * To assess, operate and improve this website and the services provided through it.
    * To keep you informed about Faith and our services and about this website.
    * If we are required to disclose such Personal Information by any applicable law, regulation or legal process.
    * To transfer any such Personal Information to other companies within the same group of companies as Faith Shoe Group Ltd, subject to the same privacy policy. 
  * In addition to the use of your Personal Information as described above, Faith may also gather anonymous information which may be used by Faith or shared with third parties. This is information which does not identify you, but which may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving this website or our services provided through it.  

  * Faith’s website may, from time to time, use cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes and they can make the World Wide Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is normal practice and many websites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Cookies do not personally identify an individual user of a computer but they do identify the computer being used. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies.  

  * We use Google Analytics to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To capture the required data Google Analytics uses 'cookies' . An excerpt taken from Google's privacy policy is below but please visit <http://www.google.com/privacy.html> if you require further information.

> **_How does Google use cookies for Google Analytics?_**  
>  _Google Analytics is Google's free web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how their visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics collects information anonymously, and much like examining footprints in sand, it reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. Analytics uses its own cookie to track visitor interactions. The cookie is used to store information, such as the time at which the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so that they can improve their website and how people find it. A different cookie is used for each website and visitors are not tracked across multiple sites. Analytics requires that all websites that use it must update their privacy policy to include a notice that fully discloses the use of Analytics. To disable this type of cookie, some browsers will indicate when a cookie is being sent and allow you to decline cookies on a case-by-case basis._

  * If you have any questions or wish to have any Personal Information edited or deleted, please e-mail us at [callcentre@faith.co.uk ](mailto:callcentre@faith.co.uk)or write to us at **Ullswater House, Western Avenue Business Centre, Kendal Avenue, London, W3 0XA**
